Come with us to our first American fair.
Look how much there is to do. Okay,
three things I want to do is I want to
eat something random, I want to drink
something random, and I want to see
something random.
>> They have pig races.
>> Down where the pig races happen. It's
free, that's so good.
>> You know how people get cancelled for
going to horse races? Do you think I'll
get cancelled for going to a pig race?
>> Are you guys ready to race?
And go!
And they're off.
>> Oh it's so cute.
>> Hurdles.
>> Go!
And they're off.
>> Guys, I'm getting dizzy.
>> There you go.
>> Bye-bye.
Picture was so cute.
>> So many different food options.
>> Have a stuffed turkey leg.
>> Flaming Hot Cheetos and [music] cheese
pickles.
>> Actually, everything is wrapped in
bacon.
>> Pickles wrapped in bacon.
>> Girl, they have fried cheesecake.
>> They also love their corn, which is kind
of random.
>> Have frog legs.
>> Wait, that sounds amazing.
>> Oh my god.
>> $2.88.
>> Doughnut burger.
>> That sounds amazing.
>> I'm going to try the pickle and Dr.
Pepper drink.
>> I'm going to try the fried tiramisu and
the fried Oreo.
>> Smells disgusting. It's chicken and
pickle on it.
>> Are you going to try some with me?
>> Yeah.
>> I don't know, I kind of
>> It's actually not bad.
>> It's actually not bad. I'm not going to
lie.
>> Not as busy. Even though they're selling
this as well, is you've got a snack.
That's a good pickle.
>> They've also got pickle chips in here.
>> So that's tiramisu, and that's the Oreo.
>> [music]
>> Mhm, it's so fluffy. I want to try the
deep fried Oreo. Oh, look at that.
Ow.
>> Do you want to meet me by the corn? You
guys leave Day or Night when on this.
You can get your psychic reading done.
Do you want to know your future?
>> Yeah.
>> I know my future.
>> What is your future?
>> You're my future.
>> Can you win me a prize?
>> Okay, we're going to get 16 tickets.
>> See if he can win me anything. Good
luck, Ben.
>> You don't need luck. You've got this.
>> Okay, he's going to try this one.
Oh!
Oh,
you did it!
Thank you!
>> Hey guys,
>> Look!
>> He won a
>> He won a big pickle toy. prize. Do I
already have a big pickle?